Guide to the Cutberto Garza papers, [ca. 1989-2009]
Garza, Cutberto papers, [ca. 1989-2009]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cutberto Garza papers, [ca.1989-2009].
29-1-3145
C. Garza
17.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, and articles.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, and articles pertaining to various committees and boards in which Dr. Garza was a member; including the World Health Organization, the Food and Nutrition Board at the Institute of Medicine, and the committees concerned with dietary reference intakes.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cutberto Garza earned his B.S. in chemistry at Baylor University in 1969, his medical degree at Baylor College of Medicine in 1973 and a Ph.D. in nutrition and food science at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology in 1976.
He served as director of the Division of Nutritional Sciences at Cornell from 1988 to 1998 and again from 2003-2005. He was Vice Provost at Cornell from 1998 to 2000. Since 1998 he has been director of the Food and Nutrition Program of the United Nations University, a think-tank and community of scholars that serves as a bridge between the UN and the international academic community. In 2005 Garza took the position of academic vice president and dean of faculties at Boston College.
Prior to joining the Cornell faculty in 1988, Garza served as a professor of pediatrics at Baylor College of Medicine and as associate director for the U.S. Department of Agriculture/Baylor Children's Nutrition Research Center. He has served on numerous advisory groups for the U.S. government, the National Academies, the World Health Organization (WHO), the U.N. World Food Program and other local and international agencies. He chaired the 1999 U.S. Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee and served as chair of the Food and Nutrition Board of the Institute of Medicine from 1996 to 2002.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, and articles pertaining to various committees and boards in which Dr. Garza was a member; including the World Health Organization, the Food and Nutrition Board at the Institute of Medicine, and the committees concerned with dietary reference intakes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Garza, Cutberto.; Garza, Cutberto.; World Health Organization.; Cornell University-Faculty.; Institute of Medicine (U.S.)--Food and Nutrition Board.
Subjects:
Diet.; Nutrition.; Reference values (Medicine)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Papers are restricted to the permission of the donor until 2020.
CONTAINER LIST
- Nutrition and Diarrheal Disease Control in Developing Countries:Committee on International Nutrition Programs, June 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Background papers:workshop, Research Priorities for Investigation of the Influence of Vitamin A Supplementation on Morbidity, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Recommended Dietary Allowances (RDA), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Committee on International Nutrition Programs, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Subcommittee on Nutrition and Diarrheal Disease Control, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Subcommittee on Diet, Physical Activity and Pregnancy, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Food and Nutrition Board: Meeting, Beckman Center, Irvine, California, March 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Beckman Center, Irvine, CA, March 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole Study Center, July 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Allergenicity of Food-use Protein Hydrolysates workshop handouts, volume II, September 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Allergenicity of Food-use Protein Hydrolysates: Woods Hole, MA /Food Chemicals Codex workshop, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- WHO Expert Committee, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- WHO Subcommittee on Infant Growth: Articles, reports, correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- WHO Subcommittee for Children-Infant Growth, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Food and Nutrition Board: Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Committee on Opportunities in the Nutrition and Food Sciences, meeting #2, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- WHO Subcommittee on Children-Infant Growth, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Irvine, CA, April 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., December 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- WHO Subcommittee on Children-Infant Growth, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- WHO Expert Advisory Panel on Nutrition (Member 1993) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- WHO: Anthropometry in Infants:subcommittee report, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Report of the Subcommittee for Infants and Children of the WHO Expert Committee on Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Symposium and meeting, Washington, D.C., December 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Food and Nutrition Board: Slide presentation by Dr. C. Garza, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole Center, July 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole Center, July 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Food and Nutrition Board:correspondence and faxes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- An Evaluation of Infant Growth: World Health Organization Subcommittee for Infants on Physical Status (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Food and Nutrition Board: Background material for Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Part 1), December 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Food and Nutrition Board: background material for Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Part 2), December 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Correspondence and memoranda, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Correspondence and memoranda, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Correspondence and memoranda, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole, MA, July 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Food and Nutrition Board:e-mails, correspondence, faxes and memoranda, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Food and Nutrition Board:e-mails, correspondence, faxes and memoranda, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Food and Nutrition Board:e-mails, correspondence, faxes and memoranda, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Food and Nutrition Board:e-mails, correspondence, faxes and memoranda, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Food and Nutrition Board:e-mails, correspondence, faxes and memoranda, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., December 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., December 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- WHO: Infant Growth Reference working group meeting, January 14-16 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- WHO: Infant Growth Reference working group meeting, January 14-16 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- WHO: Infant Growth Reference working group meeting, January 14-16 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Recommended Dietary Allowances (RDAs):correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole, MA, July 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Woods Hole, MA, July 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Food and Nutrition Board: Dietary Reference Intakes (DRI) committee, Woods Hole Study Center, July 18, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Food and Nutrition Board: RDA review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Food and Nutrition Board: RDA review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Subcommittee on "Upper Reference Levels of Nutrients," Washington, D.C. (Part 1), July 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Subcommittee on "Upper Reference Levels of Nutrients," Washington, D.C. (Parts 2-4), July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Subcommittee on "Upper Reference Levels of Nutrients," Washington, D.C. (Parts 2-4), July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Subcommittee on "Upper Reference Levels of Nutrients," Washington, D.C. (Parts 2-4), July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Dietary Reference Intake Committee, Washington, D.C., October 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Food and Nutrition Board, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- WHO: Steering Committee on Growth articles, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dietary Reference Intakes (DRI) Research, Florida: correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- DRIs: Calcium Requirement correspondence,(Food and Nutrition Board), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- DRIs: Calcium Requirement correspondence,(Food and Nutrition Board), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- DRIs: Calcium Requirement correspondence,(Food and Nutrition Board), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Food and Nutrition Board:DRI correspondence and memoranda, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Food and Nutrition Board:DRI correspondence and memoranda, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Food and Nutrition Board:DRI correspondence and memoranda, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Food and Nutrition Board:DRI correspondence and memoranda, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Institute of Medicine correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Food and Nutrition Board:Institute of Medicine correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Calcium Report: Comprehensive set of reference values for dietary nutrient intakes for the healthy population in the United States and Canada, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Calcium Report: Comprehensive set of reference values for dietary nutrient intakes for the healthy population in the United States and Canada, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- NCI: Division of Cancer Prevention and Control (DCPC) Board of Science Counsellors, 19965-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- WHO: Working Group Meeting, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- CG: WHO Growth Ref, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Questionnaires and Working Papers, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- WHO: MGRS - Protocols, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- WHO: MGRS - Memos, Reports, Emails, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- WHO: MGRS - Memos, Reports, Emails, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- WHO: MGRS - Working Group on Growth Reference Protocol, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- WHO: MGRS - General Info, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- WHO: MGRS - Reports and Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- WHO: MGRS - Reports and Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- WHO: MGRS - Reports and Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study Analyses, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- WHO: MGRS - Manual of Operations, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- WHO: MGRS - "Research on the Growth of Breastfed Infants in the US" - proposal May 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- WHO: MGRS - Various Studies and Reports, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Developmental, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- WHO: Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- WHO: MGRS - Brazil, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- WHO: MGRS - Bangladesh, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- WHO: MGRS - China, 1998-00 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- WHO: MGRS - Ghana, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- WHO: MGRS - Ghana, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- WHO: MGRS - India, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- WHO: MGRS - India, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- WHO: MGRS - Norway, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- WHO: MGRS - Norway, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- WHO: MGRS - Indonesia, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- WHO: MGRS - Oman, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- WHO: MGRS - Oman, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- WHO: MGRS - Oman, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- WHO: MGRS - USA, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- WHO: MGRS - USA, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- WHO: MGRS - USA, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- WHO: MGRS - USA, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Anthropometry, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Infant Growth-Reports, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Infant Growth - Reports, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- WHO: Subcommittee for Infants and Children - report and overheads (Box 5, Folder 16)
- WHO: Subcommittee on the Uses and Interpretation of Anthropometry in Infants, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Anthropometry - Meeting, May 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Anthropometry - Meeting, May 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- WHO: Subcommittee on the Uses and Interpretation of Anthropometry in Infants, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Anthropometry, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- WHO: Subcommittee on Anthropometry, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- WHO: Subcommittee on the Uses and Interpretation of Anthropometry in Infants, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- WHO: Systematic Review Breastfeeding, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- WHO: Executive Board Session - Reports, 1993-94 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- WHO: Expert Committee - Correspondence, Memos, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- WHO: Correspondence, Memos, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- WHO: Motor Development Study, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- WHO: Motor Development, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- National Academies - Workshop on Linking Science to US Policies in Global Food and Nutrition, April 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- National Academies - Standing Committee on Biotechnology, Food, and Fiber Production and the Environment, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Academies - Standing Committee on Biotechnology, Food, and Fiber Production and the Environment, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- National Academies - Committee on Agricultural Biotechnology, Health, and the Environment - 4th committee meeting, April 2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- National Academies - Committee on Agricultural Biotechnology, Health, and the Environment - 6th committee meeting, June 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Academies - Committee on Agricultural Biotechnology, Health, and the Environment, June 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Reference Binder - Revising the RDAs - July 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Reference Binder - Revising the RDAs, July 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Food and Nutrition - Dietary Reference Intakes Committee Meeting, May 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, August 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, December 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Food and Nutrition Board, July 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Briefing Book, December 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Food and Nutrition Board- Briefing Book, July 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Briefing Book Meeting, December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Briefing Book Meeting, December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Food and Nutrition Board, July 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Food and Nutrition Board, July 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Food and Nutrition Board, December 2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Food and Nutrition Board, June 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, November 2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Food and Nutrition Board Meeting, November 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Dietary Reference Intakes Committee, July 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- DRI - Panel on Dietary Reference Intakes for Macronutrients - Briefing Book, November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- DRI - Panel, November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- DRI - Panel - November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- DRI - Standing Committee on the Scientific Evaluation of DRIs - June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- DRI Preliminary Review - Subcommittee on Interpretation and Use of the DRIs - June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- DRI Preliminary Review - June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Institute of Medicine - Strategic Planning Retreat - July 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Institute of Medicine - Board Representitves - Council Meeting - July 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- FDA - NICHD - Workshop - "Dev. of a Surveillance System for Infants and Children Ingesting New Foods, Food Ingredients, and/or Dietary Supplements" - May 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- NAREEE - Advisory Board - July 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- National Agricultural Research, Extension, Education and Economics Advisory Board - (NAREE) Advisory Board - October 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NAREE - Advisory Board - October 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- NAREE - Advisory Board - March 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NAREE - Advisory Board - March 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Research Service (ARS) - Peer Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Research Service (ARS) - Peer Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- ARS - Peer Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ARS - Peer Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- NAREEE - Ad Hoc Committee on REE Relevance and Adequacy of Funding, April 2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- NAREEE - Advisory Board, October 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- NAREEE - Advisory Board, March 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- NAREEE - Advisory Board, March 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - Briefing Book, September 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health, September 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - Background Documents, November 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - Background Documents, November 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - Documents for January 2003 meeting (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - February 2003 - 2nd Meeting (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health, February 2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - 4th Meeting, May 2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - 4th Meeting, May 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Background to Chapters, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Background to Chapters, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - 5th Meeting, July 2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health, July 2003 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health - 6th Meeting, October-November 2003 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health, October-November 2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Committee on Identifying and Assessing Unintended Effects of Genetically Engineered Foods on Human Health, December 2003 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Obesity Management - Information Kit - Sponsored by the College of Physicians and Surgeons of Columbia University, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Obesity Management - Information Kit, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Polyp Prevention Trial (PPT) - Participants Manual (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Polyp Prevention Trial (PPT) - Participants Manual (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Polyp Prevention Trial - Nutritionist Manual, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Polyp Prevention Trial - Manual of Operations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Polyp Prevention Trial - Manual of Operations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Polyp Prevention Trial - Manual of Operations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- US Dept. of Health and Hum. Services - Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- US Dept. of Health and Hum. Services - Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- United Nations University Food and Nutrition - Program Regional Directors Meeting, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Report, February 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Dietary Risk Assessment in the WIC Program - Draft Report, August 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Nutrition Monitoring Advisory Council (NNMAC) - 8th meeting, September 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NNMAC, September 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- ICSU - Reports, Correspondence, Articles, 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- International Life Sciences Institute - Memos, Conference Material, Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Fogarty International Center National Institutes of Health - Orientation Book for Advisory Board Members, September 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Fogarty International Center National Institutes of Health - Orientation Book for Advisory Board Members, September 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Word Food Program - Statements and Papers - Rome, October 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Word Food Program - Conference Background Papers - Italy, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Cornell Genomics Task Force, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Cornell Genomics Task Force, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Cornell Genomics Task Force, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- March of Dimes - Task Force for Nutrition and Optimal Human Dev. Meeting, March 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- March of Dimes - Task Force for Nutrition and Optimal Human Development Meeting, March 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- WHO - Infant Growth Reference Workshop Reports and Other Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- WHO - Growth Reference Study - Questionnaires, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- WHO - Growth Reference Study - Papers, Correspondence, Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Conference Call - Correspondence, June-August 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- WHO - Multicenter Growth Reference Study - Meetings, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- WHO - Multicenter Growth Reference Study - Meetings, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Vatican - Breastfeeding: Science and Society Working Group, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Vatican - Breastfeeding: Science and Society Working Group, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Food Security - U.S. Action Plan, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Food Security Advisory Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Food Security Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Food Security Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Food Security Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Memos, Policies, Reports (Biotechnology), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Memos, Policies, Reports - (Biotechnology), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Biotechnology Consultative Forum - Brussels, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Biotechnology Consultative Forum - Brussels, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Biotechnology Consultative Forum - Brussels, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Biotechnology Consultative Forum - Washington, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Biotechnology Consultative Forum - Final Report, December 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Memos, Papers, Reports - Biotech Debate, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Food and Nutrition Board - Memos, Papers, Reports - Biotech Debate, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)